[JUNE] Yes, ma'am.
Your Ima-Asim Homemade Vinegar
order is on the way.
Thank you so much. We hope you
order again in the future.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Perfect!
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
What's that?
It's to make the house
feel more welcoming.
You said you wouldn't
bother me.
I wasn't bothering you.
I'm doing some cleaning.
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
[PING] I'll keep an eye on
you the whole month.
Are you involved
in the scam?
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay. Bye, Ima.
Take care.
[MUSIC BECOMES ROMANTIC]
[ROMANTIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Do you need something?
[MUSIC STOPS]
You were hypnotizing me,
weren't you?
[CLEARS THROAT LOUDLY]
I'm sorry I'm late, sir.
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey, hey, hey!
Do you like Papa Ping?
Just so you know,
we used to be close.
That was before
I came here.
Did you know I have something
that you don't?
It's my face card.
Supreme.
Elite.
And platinum edition.
So, move over.
We'll see about that.
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[IN MOCKING VOICE]
"We'll see about that."
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]